[
    {
        "question":"________is used to create immutable stylesheet references",
        "options": ["stylesheet", "Interaction manager", "Redux", "None"],
        "answer":"stylesheet"
    },
    {
        "question":"To update react native with latest version what will you use?",
        "options": ["react-native init", "react-native upgrade", "Both", "None"],
        "answer":"None"
    },
    {
        "question":"________is used to create immutable stylesheet references",
        "options": ["stylesheet", "Interaction manager", "Redux", "None"],
        "answer":"stylesheet"
    },
    {
        "question":"To update react native with latest version what will you use?",
        "options": ["react-native init", "react-native upgrade", "Both", "None"],
        "answer":"None"
    },
    {
        "question":"________is used to create immutable stylesheet references",
        "options": ["stylesheet", "Interaction manager", "Redux", "None"],
        "answer":"stylesheet"
    },
    {
        "question":"To update react native with latest version what will you use?",
        "options": ["react-native init", "react-native upgrade", "Both", "None"],
        "answer":"None"
    },
    {
        "question":"________is used to create immutable stylesheet references",
        "options": ["stylesheet", "Interaction manager", "Redux", "None"],
        "answer":"stylesheet"
    },
    {
        "question":"To update react native with latest version what will you use?",
        "options": ["react-native init", "react-native upgrade", "Both", "None"],
        "answer":"None"
    },
    {
        "question":"________is used to create immutable stylesheet references",
        "options": ["stylesheet", "Interaction manager", "Redux", "None"],
        "answer":"stylesheet"
    },
    {
        "question":"To update react native with latest version what will you use?",
        "options": ["react-native init", "react-native upgrade", "Both", "None"],
        "answer":"None"
    }
]